Miracle Uchechukwu Okeke

40 Omolara Olusi, HopeVille Estate Sangotedo-Ajah +2349066306174 | mokeke185@gmail.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/okeke-miracle-414685248

OBJECTIVE

A full-stack web engineer with vast array of knowledge in various front end and backend languages, responsive frameworks, databases and code practices. Definitely not a jack of all trades, but an expert in diverse areas that interconnects across the IT industry, with the motive of becoming an integral professional. She possesses a strong talent for learning and exploring new technologies and best practices, devising solutions and solving problems without sacrificing code and product quality. Miracle however is a core JavaScript/Nodejs and Web Engineer(Reactjs). She has played a major role in some web project that demands strong use of CSS, JavaScript, Nodejs, React js and a lot others. While a student at National open university, studying computer science and other programming languages along with data structure and algorithm and I believe that my understanding of problem solving and complex algorithms are also skills that have and will continue to contribute to any overall success as a frontend engineer.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2023	National Open University of Nigeria Computer Science(B.SC in view) 2.1
2022 •	Great Learning Academy Leadership and Management
2021 •	Simplilearn Introduction to PHP

- 2020 ChampHouse Leadership Institute Imo state Basic and Advance Leadership
 - · ChampHouse Teaching Institute Imo state **ICT**
 - Ebenezer Comprehensive Sec. School, Lagos state
 - · Couraprague Intl Primary School, Lagos State

EXPERIENCE

2019

2012 -

2018 2006 -

2012

2022 -

2022

• Iron Height Engineering

WEBSITE DESIGNER/FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- · Optimizing the user experience.
- · Using HTML, JavaScript and CSS to bring concepts to life.
- Developing and maintaining the user interface.
- · Implementing design on mobile websites.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.
- · Managing software workflow.

Jan,2022 -July,2022

• Eastern Lead Express Newspaper

Receptionist/ Computer Operator

- Answer telephone calls to take messages from clients or to provide information.
- Receive walk-in customers and guests and make them comfortable
- Responds to incoming telephone calls, email, and voice mail inquiries from internal customers (within IT department) regarding computer-related problems.

• ChampHouse Leadership Institute, Imo State 2020 -2021 FRONT DESK OFFICER · Answers phone calls courteously. · Guides guests and issues guest badges. Handles client complaints. · Files documents. · Maintains schedules. · Plans business travel. · Refills office supplies. · Receives deliveries **SKILLS** • Proficient in JavaScript HTML and CSS NodeJs ReactJS MongoDB • Tools: Notepad++, Visual Studio code · Data Structure and algorithm · Task and Project Management: Git • Advanced Mathematics: Geometry, Calculus, Number theory, Combinatorics, Statistics, Algebra · Team Building

LANGUAGES

Read: EnglishWrite: English

Graphic Design Time Management

REFERENCE

• Mr Paul Okeke - "Moniepoint " Senior Mobile Engineer

· Great Communication Skills

pokeke@moniepoint.com

08139201337